dragonair.com 2019-06-17

# Customer Privacy Policy | Legal and privacy | Cathay Pacific

## Cathay Pacific Customer Privacy Policy

When you use Cathay Pacific’s1 services, you entrust us with personal information ( **Personal Data** ). This Cathay Pacific Customer Privacy Policy ( **Privacy Policy** ) sets out what information we collect, and how we use it.

This Privacy Policy also applies when you buy travel packages from us or from Cathay Holidays Limited (or its subsidiaries).

Cathay Pacific also offers the Marco Polo Club, our loyalty programme. If you are a Marco Polo Club member or a Registered Account holder, this Privacy Policy also explains how Cathay Pacific uses and shares any Personal Data in connection with your membership.

The Asia Miles programme has its own privacy policy, so if you provide any Personal Data as part of the Asia Miles loyalty programme, we recommend you take the time to read that policy as well.

### 1\. Our Commitment to Protect Your Privacy

At Cathay Pacific, we are committed to protecting your Personal Data and your privacy.  To ensure that you can make informed decisions and feel confident about sharing certain personal information with us, please read this Privacy Policy to understand who we share your Personal Data with and for what purposes, and the choices you have concerning how your Personal Data is collected and used by us. We may also provide further privacy collection notices highlighting certain uses of your Personal Data, together with the ability to opt in or out of certain uses, when we collect Personal Data from you.

The laws of certain countries require us to provide you with additional information about our processing activities and we have included separate appendices to deal with these. As well as this document, please refer to the appendices which apply to you. _ ****_

We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy, including by posting the revised policy on www.cathaypacific.com. The changes will be effective from the date of posting.

### 2\. The Personal Data We Collect

2.1 We will collect and process some or all of the following Personal Data about you:

2.2 Certain Personal Data (particularly details of your travel documentation, payment details and contact information) are required for many of our products and services and if you fail to supply such Personal Data as requested for specific services, we may be unable to deliver you the products and services in full.

### 3\. How we collect Personal Data

3.1 We will collect some Personal Data from you directly.  We will collect other Personal Data from third parties including: (a) travel agents (including corporate travel managers) and other persons that make bookings or otherwise interact with us on your behalf; (b) our service providers and agents such as our ground handling agents who assist you with check-in and boarding or our call centre agents who provide customer service; (c) third parties such as other airlines, providers of other travel-related services; (d) our third party marketing partners; (e) the third parties that we partner with in connection with the Marco Polo Club, including credit card issuers, hotel operators, retailers and restaurants; (f) operators of our partner loyalty programmes such as Asia Miles; (g) organisations which conduct credit, fraud, and other passenger checks; (h) immigration, customs, border security and law enforcement bodies, airport authorities and other government or regulatory bodies; and (i) providers of third party websites, apps and social media platforms.

3.2 If you provide us with information about other individuals, regardless of whether you are travelling together, you must tell those individuals and let them know where they can find a copy of this Privacy Policy.

### 4\. Why we collect and use your Personal Data

4.1 When you share information with us, you help us make our services to you better. Here are some of the ways we will use your Personal Data:

### 5\. Who we share your Personal Data with

In certain circumstances, we will disclose your Personal Data to third parties as described below **:**

### 6\. Marketing

6.1 We may use Personal Data for marketing and promotional purposes, including (i) for sending or showing you updates on latest news, offers and promotions in connection with our products and services (and the products and services of our group companies such as Asia Miles and third parties) (ii) for sending or showing you joint marketing offers about our travel services and packages, loyalty programmes, contests and sweepstakes, duty-free sales and ancillary services such as travel insurance, hotel transfers and car rentals; or (iii) for tailoring and tracking your interactions with internet banner advertisement and links from third party websites to our website.

6.2 We may also use Personal Data to analyse our customers’ preferences and market trends and derive insights, which we may use to tailor the types of products and offers that we present to you. This may involve us combining Personal Data that we hold about your use of our services with information that we have collected about your web usage. We may also combine information that we have collected about you with information that we have collected about our other customers in order to derive these insights and establish market trends. We may provide these insights to our third party partners and Asia Miles for their marketing and promotional purposes. We also use advertising services and products provided by third party service providers (such as marketing agencies and social media platforms) for marketing and promotional purposes, which may involve us sharing Personal Data that we hold about you with them.  

6.3 We may communicate marketing and promotions to you by post, telephone, or online (including by email or through your mobile device or via online banner advertisement) and, as appropriate and where required, we will ask you for your consent, or otherwise provide you with the opportunity to choose not to receive marketing, at the time we collect your data. 

6.4 We will provide an option to unsubscribe or opt out of further communication on any direct marketing communication sent to you. You may also opt out by contacting us as set out in paragraph 8 below.

6.5 Please note that if you choose to unsubscribe or opt out of marketing communication, we will still send you communications about your travel with us and any other services that we provide to you. Where you are a Marco Polo Club member or a Registered Account holder, you will also continue to receive administrative emails, account summaries and updates to our services.

### 7\. Transmission, storage and security of your Personal Data

#### 7.1 IT Security

No data transmission over the Internet, a website, mobile application or via email or other message service can be guaranteed to be secure from intrusion.  However, we maintain commercially reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your Personal Data in accordance with the requirements of data protection legislation. ** __**

All Personal Data we collect about you is stored on our or our subcontractors’ secure servers. We comply with our security policies and standards when accessing or using this information and restrict access to your Personal Data ** __** to those persons who need to use it for the purpose(s) for which it was collected.  You are responsible for keeping any information that we send to you confidential and for complying with any other security procedures that we notify you of.  In particular, where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our website or mobile applications, we ask you not to share a password with anyone. ** __**

#### 7.2 Exporting your Personal Data __

Your Personal Data may be transferred outside the country in which you are located, including to countries with a lower level of data protection than in the country in which you are located. ** __**

#### 7.3 Retention period __

We will retain your Personal Data for as long as is necessary for the processing purpose(s) for which it was collected and any other permitted linked purpose (for example where we are required to retain personal data for longer than the purpose for which we originally collected it in order to comply with certain regulatory requirements).  Our retention periods are based on business needs and your information that is no longer needed is either irreversibly anonymised (and the anonymised information will be retained) or securely destroyed. 

### 8\. Your rights and contacting us

#### 8.1 General rights

You have the right (subject to various exceptions and in accordance with data protection legislation in your country) to access certain Personal Data held about you and correct any inaccuracies. We may charge a reasonable fee for the processing of any data access request in accordance with data protection legislation in your country. You also have the right to raise a complaint about our processing with the data protection regulator in your jurisdiction.

#### 8.2 Right to opt out of direct marketing

You have the right to ask us not to process your Personal Data for direct marketing purposes.  You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by indicating that you do not consent to direct marketing at the point at which we collect your Personal Data.  You can also exercise the right at any time after we have collected and used your Personal data for direct marketing purposes by:

(a) following the opt-out instructions contained in the relevant communications; or

(b) updating your email subscriptions for Cathay Pacific newsletter OR for Marco Polo Club newsletter.

#### 8.3 Updating information

We will take reasonable steps to try and ensure that your Personal Data is accurate.  To help us do this, please notify us of any changes to your Personal Data.

#### 8.4 Contacting us

Customers requesting more information or clarification on specific Personal Data usage are welcome to contact us at [dpo@cathaypacific.com](mailto:dpo@cathaypacific.com) or write to us at the below mailing addresses:

The Data Protection Officer  
Cathay Pacific Airways Limited  
6th Floor Cathay Pacific City  
8 Scenic Road  
Hong Kong International Airport  
Lantau  
Hong Kong

Hong Kong Dragon Airlines Limited  
5th Floor Cathay Dragon House  
11 Tung Fai Road  
Hong Kong International Airport  
Lantau  
Hong Kong

### 9\. Use of Cookies on Cathay Pacific Group Sites

The websites of the Cathay Pacific group companies, including cathaypacific.com use cookies which, among other things, help us to improve your experience of our websites and to ensure that they perform as you expect them to.  For detailed information on how we use cookies and the purposes for which we use then, please see our Cookies Policy.

### 10\. Links to Other Sites

This website contains links to other sites that are operated by third party companies with different privacy practices.  You should remain alert when you leave our site and read the privacy statements of other websites.  We have no control over Personal Data that you submit to or receive from these third parties.

**_This notice is written in English language and may be translated into other languages. In the event of any inconsistency between the English version and the translated version of this notice, the English version shall prevail.

These Terms and Conditions were last updated on 25 May 2018.

_**

_NOTE 1  Cathay Pacific means Cathay Pacific Airways Limited, Hong Kong Dragon Airlines Limited, Cathay Holidays Limited (and its subsidiaries)_
